{
    "subject": "resource/Love_Affair_(1994_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Glenn_Gordon_Caron",
    "human_readable": "The director of Love Affair (1994 film) is Glenn Gordon Caron.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9521203637123108,
            "question": "Who directed the film Love Affair (1994)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9513996839523315,
            "question": "Did Glenn Gordon Caron write the screenplay for Love Affair (1994)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9072997570037842,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Glenn Gordon Caron."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8896913528442383,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Glenn Gordon Caron besides Love Affair?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8881418108940125,
            "question": "What is Glenn Gordon Caron known for directing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8679677248001099,
            "question": "Is Glenn Gordon Caron an actor or a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.795173704624176,
            "question": "Besides directing, what other roles has Glenn Gordon Caron held in the film industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7600939869880676,
            "question": "What genre is the film Love Affair (1994)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.659799337387085,
            "question": "What are some of Glenn Gordon Caron's notable works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4973301589488983,
            "question": "In what year was the film Love Affair released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of Love Affair (1994 film) is Glenn Gordon Caron.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7959_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Glenn Gordon Caron's notable works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7959_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Love Affair (1994)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7959_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides directing, what other roles has Glenn Gordon Caron held in the film industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7959_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7959_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7959_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7959_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7959_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7959_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7959_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7959_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7959_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7959_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7959_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while the documents mention Glenn Gordon Caron as the director of the 1994 film \"Love Affair\", they also suggest that Warren Beatty was in control and had a final cut on the movie. Additionally, one of the articles mentions that the nominal director, Glenn Gordon Caron, has a cut of his own that isn't being released, implying that Beatty's version is the one being shown to the public."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents explicitly state that \"Love Affair was directed by Glenn Gordon Caron,\" which directly supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The evidence suggests that Warren Beatty was the one in control of the film and made the final cut, with Glenn Gordon Caron's version not being released.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}